let questions = [
    {
        question: "In Python 3, the maximum value for an integer is 263 - 1:",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is false statement in python?",
        options: [
         

       "int(144)==144",
       "int('144')==144",
       "int(144.0)==144",
       " None of the above"


        ],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which operator is right-associative?",
        options: [
            " *",

           " =",

             " +",

             " %"


        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is output for −2 * 2 **3?",
        options: [
            "12",
            "64",
            "16",
            "36"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the correct function among them which can be used to write the data to perform for a binary output?',
options: [


         'Write',

       'Output.binary',

          'Dump',

      'Binary.output'


                            ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Suppose we are given with two sets(s1&s2) then what is the output of the code −S1 + S2 ?',
        options: [
            'Adds the elements of the both the sets.',

              'Removes the repeating elements and adds both the sets.',

            'It is an illegal command.',

               'Output will be stored in S1.'
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which module is used in python to create Graphics?',
options: [

 'Turtle',

'Canvas',

'Tkinter',

'Graphics'
        
      ],              ],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Syntax error in python is detected by _________at _______',
        options:[ 

 'compiler/ compile time',

'interpreter/ run time',

'compiler/ run time',

'interpreter/ compile time'            
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'What is output of following −

print(''abbzxyzxzxabb''.count(‘abb’,-10,-1))',
options: [


'2',
 '0',
'1',
'Error'
 
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of the following code?",
options: [
def f(x = 100, y = 100): 
   return(x+y, x-y) 
x, y = f(y = 200, x = 100) 
print(x, y) 
 "300 -100",

 "200 0",

 "200 100",

 "0 300"
        
            
        ],
        answer: 0
    }
];